superduperinc.com 2009-11-15

# Super Duper Inc. Privacy Policy

SUPER DUPER PRIVACY POLICY

We are deeply committed to protecting your privacy and take all reasonable steps to protect all data and information supplied to Super Duper Inc.. We protect your privacy in a variety of ways including using industry accepted security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of data used by our system. Any information given to us will never be rented or sold to third parties. We understand the importance of personal information security and are committed to personal privacy on the Internet.

Super Duper Inc. collects data from Internet users including non-personally identifiable information from its site's visitors, IP address of their server, and what pages they visited. We use this information to continuously improve our service's functionality. Super Duper Inc. also collects personally identifiable information, including email addresses, from those visitors who opt-in to receive some information from us, make inquiries or comments. We use this information to respond to visitors' communications.

Super Duper Inc. employs permission-based marketing principles: it is required to communicate only to users who affirmatively express an interest in receiving emails relevant to their interests in a particular company or product. Permission to receive emails may be granted and taken away; in other words customers may "opt-in" and "opt-out." If a person chooses to opt-out, Super Duper Inc. is required to stop sending emails to that person. Super Duper Inc. puts a high value on a person's ability to discontinue receiving unwanted email.

Super Duper Inc. utilizes temporary Cookie technology for web site traffic analysis such as the time/date of the visit, the time/date of last visit, the page viewed, the referrer, transaction information for eCommerce pages, and other data. Super Duper Inc. utilizes persistent Cookie technology for optional account log-in. Super Duper Inc. tracks click behavior in the emails it sends out. This data is used to update specific user-profile information, ascertain the areas of most interest to opt-in email recipients, and to personalize email messages to them.

If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via our system (or purportedly sent), please forward a copy of that email with your comments to [customerhelp@superduperinc.com](mailto:customerhelp@superduperinc.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy) for review.

We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time. Updated: June 26, 2009.
